Darryl Anka: 2026 is the year of
disclosure that will get people
used to the understanding that
extraterrestrials are with us
and have been with us for a long
time, and that 2027 is basically
the target date we would have
actual ETs being introduced to
us through official channels.
Jannecke Øinæs: Countries are
unsure what relationship they
have to each other, and they
seem like they're gearing up.
Darryl Anka: Well, it'll
eventually snap. People will
reach a point where enough is
enough, as long as they're
willing to act, then things will
change. Now, of course, we'll be
given opportunities to really
explore a number of different
things we've never really been
given an opportunity to explore
before. When we have open
contact. It's like we're a bunch
of children that are squabbling
and having tantrums. And
finally, the ETs show up, and
it's like the adults have
entered the room and said,
that's enough. You need to get
along. You need to learn how to
manage your planet. You need to
learn how to manage yourselves.
For the benefit of all, it's
time you learned your lessons.
It's time to move forward. If we
decided that we were going to
have Global Thermonuclear War,
they would not allow it, and
they can't allow the earth
school to be destroyed. It's too
valuable. Do humans on Earth
want to have open contact with
ETs and become part of a
galactic family? Yes or No, take
a vote, and the vote is, how do
you respond to the information
we're delivering? How do you
apply it or not in your life?
And do you then reach out to us
and say, Yes?
Jannecke Øinæs: Darryl Anka, a
warm welcome back to the wisdom
from North show. How are you?
Darryl Anka: I'm good, Jannecke,
how are you today?
Jannecke Øinæs: I'm very good,
and I'm so excited to have you
here. We had such a rich
conversation the last time a few
years ago. It was very well
received. And now we're also
going to meet each other in
Sedona at the Sedona ascension
retreat in March, and I'm really
excited about that. And of
course, I'll drop a link below
for anyone who's interested in
attending. So today, I have tons
of questions as always, but I
want to introduce you. For those
who are new to you, you are a
world famous Channeler of the
extraterrestrial being called
Bashar who exists in a parallel
reality, or the future, we can
say, and you've been doing so
for more than 40 years. Yeah,
and and through Bashar is
teaching you are delivering
multi dimensional guidance and
wisdom. I gotta say, who many
view as the most compelling and
dynamic information delivered to
this day, to this planet, which
is amazing.
Darryl Anka: Thank you.
Jannecke Øinæs: So I want to
start by asking, How do you feel
our conversation today might
expand people's minds and
consciousness.
Darryl Anka: Well, any time
someone like yourself opens a
dialog like this and makes this
kind of exchange available to
the public. It offers other
options, other opportunities for
people to look at things from a
different perspective. It gives
them a chance to absorb
information they may not be
familiar with, to ponder it, to
decide whether it's a choice
that would lead them in a new
direction in their lives or not.
So I think you know, having
these conversations is not only
adding to our ability to have
more choices, to move forward in
our lives in positive and
constructive ways, to explore
new things, but you know, it
also allows the society as a
whole to realize that it's okay
to explore a number of things
that in the past may have been
called sort of outside the
boundaries of, you know,
rationality or whatever, but
they do have foundations to them
that actually are rooted In our
physical reality. And in I think
it gives people a chance to to
understand that, to explore
that, and to to understand how
when people do absorb and apply
the principles that we're
talking about into their lives,
there is actually a positive
effect. Their lives do get
better, and therefore they kind
of prove to themselves by
applying the information that
these principles that have been
around for 1000s of years, but
which are only really being sort
of rediscovered in modern times,
can make an impact in our
society and change things in
ways to create a world that we
would prefer.
Jannecke Øinæs: Yeah, and I'd
love to go into the five step
formula later on and really dive
deep into that. But before, I
think my audience and many
others are really curious about
the pivotal year of 2027 which
Bashar has been saying
everything will change. Has been
saying everything will change.
And it's all leading up to that.
And, yeah, I would love to just
go there, because he's saying
that open contact is imminent,
and that within two years, our
society will be introduced to
most likely hybrids, Pleiadians
and many other species. Yeah.
Could you expand on that?
Darryl Anka: Yeah, and he's not
the only one saying that there
are other psychic mediums that
have picked up upon that
particular wave of change, and
have said, basically, yeah,
we're looking roughly at about
two years for the disclosure of
all UFO information, for open
contact to begin, for the public
to be made aware of the fact
that we're not alone and never
have been alone. And so I think
that that's still on track, as
far as I understand, that 2026
is the year of disclosure of a
lot of information that will get
people used to the understanding
and used to the idea that
extraterrestrials are with us
and have been with us for a long
time, and that that 2027, is
basically the target date for
when we would be made publicly
aware of that fact, and that we
would have actual ETs being
introduced to us through
official channels. Now my
understanding is that certain
factions of extraterrestrials,
what we refer to as hybrid
extraterrestrials. And these are
these are not human beings.
They're beings that are a mix of
Homo sapiens and
extraterrestrial genetics that
were not born on earth, but have
been brought to Earth, but look
human enough that they can
mingle among us, work among us,
and they have been living and
working among us for a while,
helping with certain scientific
advancements, certain
sociological advancements,
environmental advancements,
quietly behind the scenes, but
my understanding is that the
first stage of open contact
would Be the revelation of who
these beings actually are. They
know who they are, of course,
but right now they're keeping it
secret because it's not time yet
for them their presence to be
revealed among us. But when open
contact occurs, they will be the
first level, shall we say, of
extraterrestrials we'll be able
to interact with, and as we get
used to doing that, then we will
be introduced to more and more,
let's say pure extraterrestrial
beings, Pleiadians and so forth.
Over the next couple of decades,
will be integrated more and more
into our society, or perhaps
more precisely, we will be
integrated into their society,
and, you know, become members of
a galactic family. So I believe
we're starting to see the signs
of this accelerating now with
all of these congressional
hearings on disclosure UFO
information, the fact that
they're now exploring and
examining how to create
conditions and laws for
whistleblowers and military
people to come forth with their
UFO experiences, with their
knowledge of what's going on
behind the scenes, like reverse
engineering programs and things
like that and that, they're
creating laws to protect these
people so they can come forth
with their information without
fear of ridicule, without fear
of losing their careers over
this. So that's a big change in
our society, and I see it only
accelerating. In fact, even
recently, I think one of the
whistleblowers started just
literally naming names of people
that have been involved in these
programs, who have been secretly
involved, and now they're
literally just saying, well,
this person was involved, and
this person was involved, so it
gives us something to look into.
So I see this as accelerating
through 2026 and ideally
culminating in 2027 as open
contact.
Jannecke Øinæs: Wow,
fascinating. And when you speak
about interaction, what has
Bashar said about that, are we
speaking about that the
governments and certain people
are interacting with them or us
as well? Like interacting?
Darryl Anka: Yes, we are. There
are individuals. Yes, of course,
there are encounters that happen
and things like that. But I
mean, officially, my
understanding is that there are
certain ETs that are officially
working or well behind the
scenes unofficially, I suppose,
working with scientists, working
with government officials,
certain ones, environmental
engineers, people like that,
moving our technology, moving
our understanding of our
connection to nature, forward a
bit at a time, but again, that
can accelerate when their
identities are made public,
because we'll be able to
interact with them directly. We
won't necessarily have to go
through a lot of the officials
at this point. It won't be a
secret anymore, so the first
group will be able to interact
with face to face directly. Will
be the extraterrestrial hybrids
that have already been among us
because they're already part of
our society. In a sense. We
sometimes encounter them. We
sometimes come across them. They
have the ability telepathically
to sort of get us to ignore
them. At the moment, there have
been stories and reports of, you
know, many people in society
kind of saying, Well, I ran
across this unusual individual,
and they just felt wrong. They
just felt like they didn't
belong here, or something was
odd about them. But then I just
kind of mysteriously forgot
about it and went on my day. So
there are those kinds of
crossings where we do run into
them now and then, but at this
point, because it's not
appropriate for them to reveal
who they are, they will
telepathically encourage us to
forget that we saw them, or look
away or go about our business.
When the day comes when they are
revealed to us, that won't
happen anymore. We'll be able to
interact with them directly.
Jannecke Øinæs: Interesting. And
why is this happening now? Is
that because we have increased
our vibration, because I do see
some sort of a paradox there.
And I had a woman reaching out
to me. She is a great fan of
your work, and she said, Could
you please ask this question to
Daryl, because we see world
leaders today who have a mindset
of power and war and control,
and wouldn't they see this as a
threat and act accordingly?
Darryl Anka: Yes, well, again,
they're operating out of fear.
You have to understand that
what's going right now on, right
now in the world, with all the
chaos and uncertainty and
attempts to control everything
and attempts to gain power, are
really reactions to feeling
powerless. These people operate
out of fear. They don't feel
connected, they don't feel
powerful, they're extremely
insecure, and therefore they
have to sort of reach out
physically and try to control
their environment, to give them
some semblance of the idea of
power. And of course, this is
not true power. This is simply
the attempt to cover up the fact
that they feel powerless, that
they feel less than that.
They're full of fear that
anything will change to expose
the idea that they believe is
true about themselves, which is
that they are powerless, which
isn't true. They just don't
understand what real power is,
what real connection to Source
is. They don't understand these
things, but this is chaos now,
because we're getting all of
this up, out into the open, out
of our systems, so everyone can
see very, very plainly what the
negative side is like. So we can
see, by contrast, more clearly,
what the positive choices are
that we need to make to turn the
world around. So that's why all
of this is coming out into the
public, why it's being put on
the table. It's, you know,
agents of change, both positive
and negative, still serve to
change things by demonstrating
things we do prefer and things
we don't prefer much more
blatantly and much more clearly,
so that there's no confusion
between the two, so that we can
finally say, Okay, this doesn't
work for us. We need to make a
change. And we're seeing more
and more and more options coming
up with recent events all over
the world about things that we
simply will no longer abide,
that we have to do something
about, that we have to take
steps to change, so that we're
doing so for the benefit of
humanity in general, and not
just for the benefit of the few.
Jannecke Øinæs: Yeah, because I
do think it's interesting to
have a sense that the tension in
the world is increasing and the
polarity is increasing, and that
countries are unsure what
relationship they have to each
other, and they seem like
they're gearing up. Does Bashar
say anything about how this will
culminate, where this is going?
Darryl Anka: Well, it'll
eventually snap. People will
reach a point where it's enough
is enough, and they will finally
do something about it. So again,
we can use this to our
advantage. Bashar often refers
to this as the rubber band
analogy. The farther back you
pull a rubber band, when you
finally let go, it'll fly that
much farther and faster in the
opposite direction. So
basically, he's saying, the
farther back you pull this
rubber band into negativity,
when you finally let go, it
finally snaps, it'll fly that
much faster and farther into the
light, into a positive reality.
So we can use the momentum of
all the buildup in the negative
side, of things that are
happening to actually propel and
push us into the positive side
much more quickly, because when
it finally snaps, it'll change
relatively fast. So we're using
that momentum to our advantage,
or we can do so as long as
people are willing to step up
and do things that will help
others, that will serve
humanity, that will make
changes, as long as they're
willing to act, then things will
change. Now, of course, we'll be
given opportunities to really
explore a number of different
things. We've never really been
given an opportunity. To explore
before when we have open
contact, because then it will be
kind of like, and I certainly
don't mean this in a judgmental
way, but it's an relatively apt
analogy. It's like we're a bunch
of children that are squabbling
and having tantrums, and finally
the ETS show up, and it's like
the adults have entered the room
and said, that's enough. You
need to get along. You need to
learn how to manage your planet.
You need to learn how to manage
yourselves for the benefit of
all. Stop fighting, stop
squabbling, stop throwing
tantrums, stop feeling less than
this is the way the universe
works. We're here to help you.
We're here to tell you it's time
you grew up. It's time you
learned your lessons. It's time
to move forward. That's my
interpretation of what's
happening with open contact. The
adults are stepping into the
room,
Jannecke Øinæs: And how long
would you say that they have
been here? Because you said
Darryl Anka: 1000s of years,
maybe longer. But the thing of
it is, see, this is the ironic
thing is, when we talk about
open contact, in a sense, we're
really just talking about the
revelation of the existence of
ETs for Western culture, because
indigenous cultures around the
world have been saying that
they've been in contact with ETs
for 1000s of years. This is not
new to them. They have been
interacting with ETs because
their cultures are very open and
willing and recognizing that
we're all part of a bigger
family. And they talk about star
beings and the star people and
the star ancestors, they've been
talking about that for 1000s of
years, and Western culture
hasn't been paying attention. So
open contact is really about the
last culture on Earth, as
widespread as it might be,
finally, understanding what
indigenous cultures have
understood for 1000s of years,
ETs have been here, in a sense,
they've never gone away. There
have been waves of when more of
them might be here or less of
them might be here for various
reasons, based on what's
happening on Earth and how our
evolution is happening, they
sometimes take a little bit of a
hands off policy to let us
evolve, to let us grow, to let
us learn our lessons. But then
over certain periods of time,
they have come back again and
again and again and said, Okay,
what have you learned? We're
here now. Can we move forward?
So I think we are reaching the
end of the cycle of them, sort
of being quiet, behind the
scenes, leaving us alone, more
or less, but now we're starting
a new cycle where they're
showing up again. They're
saying, Okay, it's time for us
to enter the room. It's time for
you to recognize more and more
UFO sightings are happening,
more reports, more encounters
are happening around the world,
and more things are changing
with regard to your recognition
that we exist. So it's now time
for us to come back, reveal
ourselves and show you that we
can all move forward together in
a more positive way. It's time
for that chapter of humanity's
evolution to begin. ETS have
been helping with a lot of
different technologies, space
technology, energy technologies,
AI, technologies, things like
that. So I think that when open
contact occurs, we'll get a
fuller understanding of what
their involvement has been,
about, how they've been helping
move us forward with that, and
along with it, will come some
ideas and instructions for how
they have utilized AI in
positive ways and give us the
understanding of how we can do
the same. So the only thing I
would call an intervention or an
interference would be to prevent
us from annihilating ourselves.
That's where their hands off.
Policy ends. If we decided that
we were going to have Global
Thermonuclear War. They would
not allow it. That would destroy
the whole thing, and they won't
allow that Earth is too valuable
a school for souls to be
destroyed. So while they will
not be able to stop local
skirmishes, because that's up to
us to do something as
destructive as a world war with
nuclear weapons would release so
much energy it would actually
interpenetrate into different
dimensions. In other words, it
wouldn't stay in our own
backyard. Therefore, they can't
allow that, and they can't allow
the earth school to be
destroyed. It's too valuable. So
the idea is they have, and there
are many reports of this. They
have demonstrated this fact over
and over again by having UFOs
appear over missile silos,
scrambling the launch codes,
shutting down the launch codes.
The one, very famous one is in
the mound. From Air Force base
where they, you know, a glowing
red UFO shut down all the launch
codes and scramble them. So
we've been shown again and again
and again, in no uncertain
terms, you will not be allowed
to launch these things. That's
the one area where they will
intervene and will stop us from
annihilating ourselves.
Jannecke Øinæs: Hey, guys, I
want to jump in here to give my
thanks for being part of the
Wisdom From North community.
Your support and engagement
means the world to us. We put so
much passion, so much love into
these episodes, and my intention
is really to be part of this
great shift of consciousness, to
do what I can do with this
channel, to help people expand
their consciousness, love
themselves more, follow their
purpose and shine their light.
So if you haven't yet
subscribed, I would love for you
to do so thank you so much.
You'll find the link somewhere
here below. And now let's go
back to the episode. Well,
that's good to know that they're
taking care of us in that sense.
Darryl Anka: Well, yeah, you
know, they see this as an
extremely important school for
souls, for advancement, for
understanding how to transform
darkness into light, positive
out of negative and freedom out
of limitation. It's a very
advanced school, and souls can
accelerate very rapidly here if
they're willing to learn the
lessons that the challenges in
life brings them in this
particular kind of a reality. So
they don't want to lose that in
the galaxy, it's relatively not
that it's the only only one, but
it's relatively rare, the mix of
things that exist here, and the
way in which we experience them.
It's a it's a very unique
school.
Jannecke Øinæs: Yeah, I've heard
that before. When you say they,
from my understanding, there are
infinite different species out
there in the galaxy. So who are
you referring to? Is it a
specific group of
extraterrestrials?
Darryl Anka: Yes, I think we're
dealing with a few groups. We're
not, obviously not dealing with
every extraterrestrial in
existence, because that probably
is a relatively infinite number,
or certainly so large. We can't
even imagine what that number
might be. But there are certain
groups that are connected to,
associated with and involved
with humanity's evolution, the
hybrids certainly because
they're genetically part of us,
the Pleiadians, Arcturians,
Lyrans, Tall Whites, the grays,
of course, of all different
stripes, because there are many
different factions of grays,
they can't be lumped into one
particular thing. And there are
several others that people have
encountered that seem to be
relatively common, Reptilians,
things like that. Now, again,
you know there are different
kinds of agendas here, different
kinds of interactions. Even
though there is an overall
agenda of preserving the earth
and moving humanity forward,
they can still each have their
own way of going about this, a
way of discussing what is best
for everyone, how we fit into
the Galactic Family, so on and
so forth, or the Federation that
we will ultimately become
members of in the decades ahead.
So, yeah, I think we're dealing
maybe roughly with about a dozen
species or so right now. As far
as I can tell, there may be, you
know, a few others that come and
go, that they're not really
deeply involved, but they may
have research mission, missions
of observations, taking samples,
things like that, for their own
purposes. So there may be more
than that that have visited us.
But in terms of the main group
that is really connected and
concerned with our evolution, I
think we may be dealing with
somewhere around about a dozen
different species, roughly.
Jannecke Øinæs: And would you
say it's possible, for instance,
to use AI to connect with them,
for those who really want to
connect with ETs? Is it
possible, for instance, to use
chatGPT and Gemini to write to
them and connect in that way? Or
do we need to go inside?
Darryl Anka: Well, I mean
writing something in any format,
even if you're writing it on a
piece of paper, in a sense, is
going inside because you're
expressing what is inside of you
outwardly, and even talking out
loud, can connect you to them.
Remember, they're extremely
sensitive, extremely telepathic.
They can pick up on what you're
saying. So I'm not sure it
really makes a difference
whether we use chatGPT, or
whether we simply talk out loud,
or whether we write things down
in a journal. I think all of
these are expressions outward
expressions of an inner desire
to make a connection, and
they'll pick up on the energy of
that nomatter what medium you
use to do that in. So it's not
so much that we have to use AI
to do that. It's just a matter
of being willing to express it
outwardly in some concrete form,
even speaking out loud, and
they'll telepathically pick up
on what they need to pick up on.
I mean, the whole reason why
we're seeing an acceleration is
because so many people are
desirous of the truth, desirous
of what's going on, to know
what's going on really behind
the scenes. And that's why we're
seeing, you know, more and more
disclosure of information coming
out about ETs and UFOs and
things like that. That is a
response to what we've been
putting out there as a kind of
invitation for them to show
themselves, because inside, we
deeply know we're not alone. We
know they're here on some level.
I usually call this the biggest
secret that everyone already
knows. You know, because when
you really start talking to
people, they don't really talk
about it much in public, but
when you have an ability to talk
to people in they feel safe
responding to you, they will
tell you, more often than not,
that they've had what they think
is a sighting, that they've had,
what they think is an encounter,
that they've had, An unusual
experience that can probably be
translated as some sort of
extraterrestrial or spiritual
contact. More people have these
kinds of experiences than we're
willing to admit publicly, and I
think that's starting to come
out because people are starting
to feel a little safer talking
about their experiences because
of all the stuff that's coming
out about disclosure along
official lines. So once it's
okay along official lines, once
people start to feel like, well,
people won't call me crazy for
saying this, then they're
willing to talk about their
experiences. And I think we'll
find out that many more people
have had these experiences than
we know of.
Jannecke Øinæs: And is it a
friendly universe? Can we trust
that they're benevolent?
Darryl Anka: The ETs that we're
dealing with are benevolent. I
mean, you know, this is kind of
an old chestnut that people have
asked about and mentioned, but
really, when you think about how
advanced they are, if they
weren't benevolent, I'm not sure
why they wouldn't have taken us
over a long, long time ago,
before we had any ability to
resist at all, if you know, and
the other the other side of this
coin, when people really stop
and think about it, is, look, if
you have the ability to traverse
the stars, there are so many
resources out there that you
have access to one planet is
nothing to them. They can go
anywhere they want to get
anything they need. They don't
need to take over a planet or
destroy civilization. And the
third aspect of this is they
operate from true intelligence.
I don't think humanity really
even understands what true
intelligence actually looks
like, but one of its calling
cards is to operate on whole
systems, to see the entire thing
as one system. So intelligent,
ETs are looking at the universe
as one system. Everything's
interconnected, just like you
look at the ecosystem of a
planet, everything is necessary.
If you get rid of one thing, you
have thrown the entire system
out of whack, out of balance.
They look at the universe that
way. So ETs that are truly
intelligent are never going to
have designs on wiping out or
taking over a civilization in
that way, because then the
civilization is not being left
to add its uniqueness to the
whole system. And there are
things even ETs can learn from
what our experiences here on
Earth are as souls, learning
lessons about positive and
negative reality, about
polarity, so, about
transformation, you know? So
they look at this as a valuable
piece of the universe, a
valuable expression. They're
never going to try and eliminate
something that's a part of a
system that they belong to,
because that would deprive them
of things they need to that's
the way true intelligence looks
at the universe as one whole
system.
Jannecke Øinæs: And let's go
into Bashar as teachings. How
does he look at reality? I think
he has four or five steps where
he explains how reality the
basis of reality. And also, I
know there is part of a law of
attraction in there. I'm curious
whether that is where he speaks
about the whole universe,
whether every single planet and
civilization has the same
understanding, understanding,
yeah,
Darryl Anka: in general, well,
not. I mean, can't speak for
every civilization out there,
the ones that are dealing with
us. Yes, they do so. I have the
same or similar understanding
of, like I said, how to
approach, you know, your
relationship with source, with
all that is, whatever you want
to call it, with existence, with
the universe, and generally,
basically, there are two sets of
five things here. There are what
Bashara refers to as the five
laws. And there are the five
steps of the formula that define
how we create our reality,
experience, our experience of
reality. So the five laws, these
are universal, extra
dimensional. They can't be
changed. They're the same
everywhere. They're five
fundamental things about
existence itself that never
change. And this is, you exist.
You cannot cease to exist.
Existence is its own state. The
one is the all. The all are the
one. In other words, everything
is made out of the same one
thing. Everything is here and
now. Basically, everything
exists in the same moment, and
space and time are essentially
projections of consciousness,
and are illusionary. In a sense,
they serve a purpose, but
they're projections of
consciousness. What you put out
is what you get back. And this
is sort of the basis of the law
of attraction, is whatever
vibrational frequency you give
off, because everything is
energy in vibration, energy
vibrating at different
frequencies. That's how you
create the difference between
one thing and another. Why you
see differences in the one is
that there are different
vibrational frequencies within
it that translate into different
things. But what you put out,
what vibration you put out, is
basically determining what you
experience in life, because
everything is nothing but a
mirror. It's reflecting back to
you, and the fifth is,
everything changes except the
laws. Change is the only
constant. Everything is
constantly shifting, constantly
changing, except the laws. So
those are the five laws. And
that's true everywhere the
formula, what he calls the
formula, the five steps of the
formula are more for how you
apply, how you live, how you
thrive in physical reality. By
doing these five steps, it's
literally like being handed an
instruction manual for this is
how you're already creating your
reality experience, but you're
doing it unconsciously. I'm
giving you the instruction
manual to show you is what he's
saying, what it is you're
actually doing. So you can do it
more consciously and create an
effect and an outcome that is
more preferable and more
positive, and done more
consciously with more awareness.
So the five steps of the formula
or the instruction manual are.
Number one, you act on whatever
is representative of your
passion first, because passion,
you know, I mean, we've heard
this for a long time. You know,
live your dream, follow your
bliss, act on your passion.
Bashar answers why that's
important. He doesn't leave it,
you know, up in the air as just
a euphemism. The reason it's
important is because what we
call the sensation of passion or
excitement or creativity or love
is our physical body's
translation of an energy message
from our soul. Our soul operates
on a certain high frequency. Our
physical mind operates on a more
limited frequency, or a lower
one, if you want to say that,
but the soul is attempting to
guide the physical mind, and it
does so because it's non
physical. It has to do so
through messages that come in
the form of energy vibrations,
energy frequencies, our physical
minds and our physical bodies
translate that vibrational
message into the sensation we
call passion and excitement. So
the reason it's important to act
on your excitement is because
this is your soul saying, This
is who you are. This is the next
step on your path. You have to
trust it. You have to act on it.
This is what's going to keep you
aligned with your soul so you
act on it. That's number one,
first and foremost. But you have
to make sure that it truly is
your excitement. You can't just
gloss it over and say, Oh yes,
this is more exciting than
anything else because you're in
denial or in fear about what
what would actually be your true
path, and you're just trying to
cover up your anxiety by
pretending it's excitement. You
have to be honest with yourself
about what your passion truly is
all about. And there are several
things that go with that we go
deeply into, that another. Your
time. The second principle after
acting on your passion is to
take it as far as you can until
you can take it no further. In
other words, you act on every
opportunity that comes to you,
or you even make opportunities
that don't exist to act on it,
and you take it as far as you
can until either the excitement
naturally wanes, making sure
you're not the one killing the
excitement with a fear based
belief. But when it naturally
wanes, then you look for the
next thing. Or when you have no
more ability to act on it, you
look for the next thing that is
more exciting than anything
else. And this can be everyday
things too, taking a walk,
reading a book, talking to a
friend, and you act on that next
and you keep doing that the
third thing, and this is one of
the more challenging things for
most people, is you act on your
excitement with zero assumption
and zero insistence on what the
outcome is supposed to look
like. Because the truth is is,
while you may think you imagine
what an ideal outcome might be,
the truth is, you have no clue
what that actually is going to
look like. You may guess
sometimes correctly, but
ultimately, you really don't
know, but if you use
visualization, if you use a
symbol of what the ideal outcome
can be, to get into the state of
excitement and passion about
something happening that would
be at least representative of
your vision, then you drop the
vision, then the soul can bring
you what is actually
representative of that vision,
of that energy level that you
used the vision to get to.
That's the important thing about
visualization, is not insisting
that your particular picture has
to come to pass. Sometimes it
might, but it's not insisting or
assuming that that's the ideal
outcome, because what to the
physical mind seems to be the
ceiling to the soul is just the
floor, and it can give you
something much better than you
were capable of imagining with
your physical mind, if you let
it so you use visualization to
get into the state of
receptivity and excitement and
passion, using the visualization
as a symbol of an ideal outcome,
but then you don't insist on
what you've pictured, so that
what needs to come to you can
actually come which could be
many times better than you
imagined. The fourth step is
that you stay in a positive
state no matter what happens.
You don't apply automatic
negative meaning to anything.
I'm not saying you start calling
negative things positive things,
but you stay in a positive
state. And even if something was
created out of negative
intention by someone else, it
doesn't mean it will affect you
negatively. If you stay in a
positive state, that positive
vibration will filter out any
negativity and allow you to get
a benefit from that experience,
even if it was initiated
negatively by someone else.
Staying in a positive state
again is what you put out, is
what you get back. It's that law
of attraction again, so staying
in a positive state will also
give you the ability to receive
inspirational thoughts and ideas
that will move you forward,
using the incident and the
situation, even though it may
have started negatively in a
more positive way, or getting
something positive out of it.
Let me make a side note here
about the law of attraction.
Also. It's not wrong that you
have to be in the proper
vibration to experience certain
things that are the equivalent
of that frequency. That's not
wrong. Where I think people have
a misunderstanding of the Law of
Attraction is that they believe
they have to learn to get into
that vibrational state. You
don't your soul is already
giving off the frequency that
automatically attracts
everything you need in life that
will fulfill you. It's not an
issue of having to learn what
that frequency is. The issue is
getting out of the way of that
frequency and allowing it to
bring you what you need by
letting go of fear based and
negative beliefs that block your
innate frequency from attracting
those things to you, so you
don't have to learn the
frequency. You have to learn to
stop blocking the frequency with
negative beliefs and clear
yourself out. Now the fifth step
is to examine your belief
systems, to let go of the
negative ones, the fear based
ones, to realize that those are
probably things you picked up
along the way growing up from
your parents, your school, your
friends, society, and they're
not really about you. They're
about who you were dealing with
at the time growing up, because
you didn't know the difference
really in what was about you and
what was about them. But as
adults, you can start to start.
See that. I mean, you can always
say, well, when someone presents
something to you, it's always an
opportunity to go, yes, do they
have something that I need to
understand, that will improve
me, that will make me a better
person? But once you decide that
that's not true, then anything
coming from them, you can
realize, well, it's not my
issue, it's their issue, and
maybe I need to do something to
help them deal with that issue,
because that's why they're in my
life. When we talk about people
being a reflection of you, we
don't necessarily mean a one to
one reflection. When someone
comes into your life that has a
particular negative issue, that
doesn't mean you have the same
issue. It may mean that. But
again, with honest self
investigation, you get to decide
whether or not they have
something to give you that you
need to apply to yourself to be
a better person. But if you
decide, after self examination,
that that has nothing to do with
you, then you can recognize
they're in my life as a
reflection of what I am willing
to do to help someone else
improve their lives. That's the
reflection I'm looking at. Is a
reflection of my willingness to
be of service to someone, to
help them. So those are the five
steps of the formula and the
five laws that are a description
of the structure of existence,
because you have to understand
the structure of existence never
changes. It is what it is. The
constant changing is a change of
relationship to it, of
experience of it, of perspective
of it. That's how creation
expands. Is that we constantly
change our relationship to it,
but the structure is always the
same.
Jannecke Øinæs: Thank you for
mapping that out in such great
detail. I really appreciate
that. And from what I
understand, Bashar is sharing
this from his own experience of
how he and his species evolved,
right?
Darryl Anka: Yeah, and his
observations of different
civilizations, including ours,
because he is a first contact
specialist. So he is one of the
people in his society that
actually initiates first contact
with different civilizations,
and this is usually the way. In
most cases they go about it.
They find a way or a willing
participant who is willing to go
into a state that allows the
information to telepathically be
delivered to that society, and
then they watch, what does that
society do with that
information? Do they use it to
their benefit? Do they open up
their understanding of what
we're talking about? Does it
make them more vibrationally
compatible with our society or
not? And if it makes us more
vibrationally compatible, then
the sharing of this information
is one of the steps that leads
to open contact. If it doesn't
make us more vibrationally
compatible, it leads us away
from open contact, because then
they're saying, well, they're
not ready, and we're not going
to force ourselves on anyone.
This is us testing the waters.
Do humans on Earth want to have
open contact with ETs and become
part of a galactic family? Yes
or No, take a vote, and the vote
is, how do you respond to the
information we're delivering?
How do you apply it or not in
your life? How do you upgrade
your vibration to know who you
really are, to know yourselves
as souls in this universe. And
do you then reach out to us and
say, yes, we want to interact
with you. We want to be part of
a bigger family, or do we want
to just stay in our own little
planet and leave us alone, we
still have that choice.
Jannecke Øinæs: Yeah, yeah, I
think we're coming to
understanding that we are co
creating. It's not them and us
and they're above us, and it's
their choice. We are emanating
our beliefs and choices
absolutely synchronicities.
Where does that come into the
picture? Is it like this that
when you pay attention to
synchronicities, they become
miracles? Yeah.
Darryl Anka: Well, miracles,
according to Bashar, are the
natural order of things. They're
not the exceptions. It's when we
start seeing how the universe
actually works. Synchronicity is
linear space times way of
showing us that everything is
connected to everything else,
that there are no accidents,
that it's all an orchestration,
that everything works out in
perfect timing, and that when we
start experiencing more of that
orchestration, more of that
synchronicity, then we know
we're operating in a higher
vibration, because we're seeing
the interconnectedness of
existence more often and
experiencing that
interconnectedness more often.
And therefore that's how you
know that your vibration is
going up, because more
synchronous. City is one of the
ways that is the response from
the universe to another level
that you're operating on, where
your senses are able to start
picking up on the fact that
everything is an orchestration.
Everything is working together,
that there are no accidents, and
that all life paths are
interconnected and intertwined
for various reasons. Now,
sometimes when you're in a
certain situation, that
situation may not have, let's
say, as many lessons in it for
you as it might have for someone
else in the situation, but it's
still an orchestration because
you're willing to participate in
it in order to be of service, to
allow whoever needs to get
something more out of it, to get
something more out of it. So
this is what I mean, is you can
unconsciously participate. I
mean, let's say you're stuck in
a traffic jam. Well, you're
there because there's a reason
for that traffic jam to someone,
someone may have been rushing at
80 miles an hour down the
freeway, and if they had kept
doing so, they would have gotten
into an accident and died by
orchestrating a traffic jam.
They now can't so you may never
know why that kind of
orchestration happened. You can
try and get some lessons out of
it. You can say, Well, okay,
maybe this is a sign I need to
slow down in life. Maybe I am
rushing into things. Maybe I
need to take some time to look
around me and see who's around
and who's next to me, and feel
the connections I have to other
members of my society and so on
and so forth. You can start
looking at it that way, and you
will start learning things about
it that way. But you can also
realize I may be here because
I'm simply willing to be of
service to others who may be
getting more out of this
experience than I am at the
moment, but that's okay, because
I'm doing this to be service to
them, to help them get what they
need. It's not about me, it's
about them. So you have to start
looking at life as an
orchestration in order to start
seeing life and experiencing
life from that perspective. And
when you start doing that, you
start realizing synchronicity is
all over the place. It's
everywhere. It's in everything.
It is space times way of showing
you that it's all an
orchestration, that it's all
connected, there are no
accidents,
Jannecke Øinæs: which means also
there are no coincidences at
all. I love that, but I also
loved how you explained that.
I've never heard it. Heard it in
that way. I've heard, sort of
some channelers say, you know,
not everything is pre planned or
orchestrated. There are some
things that are not like, for
instance, me dropping this pen
right now
Darryl Anka: what, of course,
what they mean is, as a soul,
you put certain challenges on
your life path, those are pre
planned. There may be a few
different ways of experiencing
those things, maybe at a
different timing, maybe on a
different scale, maybe with
different props. So yes, we're
not saying, Okay, I'm going to
pick up this pencil now, and I
pre plan to do something like
that, you use the props that are
available to you, but the idea
is, maybe, what do you do with
that pencil? Is it something
that allows you to learn that
you have the ability to draw
something beautiful? That would
be the pre planned thing,
whether you picked up a pencil,
a pen or a paintbrush, probably
doesn't matter. You use what's
available as a set of props to
accomplish what the soul laid
out as an expression of
creativity in your life, and
artistic expression, that's
what's planned out. But there
may be a variety of ways that
that can be done, and a variety
of scale and scope upon which it
can be experienced. Do you draw
a picture just for your friend
and lighten up their life by
receiving that as a gift? Do you
make paintings that millions of
people see that changes their
life because of how it looks? So
do you do it now? Do you do it
later. Do you slowly? Do you do
it quickly? How many people do
you affect? How many expressions
of your passion do you put out
there? And in what way you have
the free will to determine how
you will experience the
challenges that you as a soul
laid out on your life, but the
soul's Free Will choices to have
those experiences, to have those
challenges, are what we
typically refer to as our
destiny. We can't change what
the soul has decided it needs to
learn as a lesson for its
growth, but we have the freedom
as the physical version of our
souls to determine how. We will
experience that challenge
positively, negatively, happily,
sadly, with great gusto. With
you know on we quickly, slowly.
It's up to us to determine how
we experience it, but we will
face that challenge in some way,
shape or form, because that's
what our soul decided it needed
for its true growth.
Jannecke Øinæs: That makes
sense. I want to jump over to
reality. Many speak about a
split coming up, right? Well,
I'm going there because many
speak about that we have our own
reality. We on that the last
time as well. And then we also
hear the talk about a split,
like two realities together.
Darryl Anka: Okay. The idea is,
look, we're interacting right
now, you and I. You're not
interacting directly with me.
Are you? You're interacting with
an electronic recreation of my
sound and my image, right?
You're not seeing me directly.
This is the way reality is
actually structured. It's
structured holographically. When
you are even face to face with a
person, you are interacting
directly with a soul, but you're
not actually seeing them
directly. You are creating in
your reality your version of
them. You have no idea whether
or not your version of them is
the same as their version of
themselves. They may see
themselves very differently and
experience themselves very
differently, and they may see
you very differently and
experience you very differently
than you experience yourself. So
we each have our own reality in
which we use our consciousness
and our energy to create our
versions, our representations of
other beings we are interacting
with on a higher level, but
these physical representations
are like what we are
experiencing right now in this
conversation. They are
simulations, in a sense, they
are avatars, in a sense, and we
use these to then create the
kind of reality that we prefer
and populate it with the
versions of everyone else that
are commensurate with the
reality we believe in most
strongly To be true. So where
our versions of reality are
similar, we can interact in the
way that we're interacting right
now, where they're not similar
at all. There's no interaction
people that interact with others
whose vibration is not at all
similar to the mass consensus.
Are called crazy. It doesn't
mean they're not actually
interacting with someone. It's
just that the mass consensus
can't see them because their
vibration is too different from
what we collectively agree
should be the reality that we're
sharing or experiencing, but
we're all each only creating
that reality for ourselves as an
interface based on an agreement
of what we say is important for
us to experience as reality At
this moment. Does this make
sense?
Jannecke Øinæs: A little bit.
Okay, you explained it to me the
last time as well. And I'm still
my mind is like, that's okay.
That's okay. Really getting it
comes to the split between 3D
and 5d
Darryl Anka: Oh, no no no, no,
no, no, no, no, no. That's a
misunderstanding that people
have. 5D is non physical,
totally non physical. That's the
spirit realm. Okay, we can use
our connection to the spirit
realm, because we're souls, to
uplift our vibration as third
density people, to bring us into
fourth density, which is still
physical. Fourth density is a
higher frequency of physical
reality of the physical
dimension. We can use fifth
dimensional, fifth density
energy to elevate us because of
our connection to that energy as
souls. But we're not splitting
into fifth density, unless you
die, then you go into fifth
density, then you're non
physical. You're a spirit.
Again, you're a soul. But the
idea of the split that Bashar is
talking about is that as each of
us chooses what to believe is
true for ourselves and for
reality, we can. Start to
diverge more and more and more,
like we're sort of seeing on the
planet right now, where people
believe one thing to be
absolutely true, and someone
else may believe to be exactly
the opposite, to be absolutely
true. And I'm talking not about
the idea of just being in denial
of the truth. I'm talking about
things that people are referring
to as things like the Mandela
effect, where I remember one
history and you remember
something else, completely
different, and both of us
actually have a real memory of
those two completely different
realities or histories. This is
because we are deciding how to
be a part of the collective
conscious consensus about, what
is our history, what is our
reality? And therefore, those
that start diverging and
choosing, for whatever reason,
something that is too different
from what another person
believes, they're starting to
diverge into different reality
streams, into different
timelines. In a sense, right
now, we allow our timeline to
contain multiple differences,
but eventually, as we continue
to diverge in the years ahead,
we will probably only experience
something that is similar in
vibration to what we believe to
be true, each of us. So we may
no longer interact with people
who believe something too
differently from us. They will
no longer literally appear in
our reality at all. So the idea
is, that's what he's defining as
the split is it's how you create
a reflection that is true for
you, that may not be
vibrationally compatible with
what is true for someone else,
to the point where, right now,
we can see each other's
vibrations, but eventually we
may not be able to, and that's
the split he's talking about, is
the experience our projection of
reality may be so different from
someone else's that we can no
longer even see a representation
of them in our reality. We can
no longer create a
representation of them in our
reality, it would be as if you
were operating on a certain
frequency in this program that's
allowing us to interact with
each other stream yard, and I
was operating on a completely
different frequency, and we
couldn't suddenly see each other
at all. It was as if the
technology diverged, the
frequency of the technology, the
style of the technology, started
to diverge enough that you would
start to lose my reception, and
I would start to lose your
reception, and then we would not
be able to interact. Right now
we're both using what we believe
to be a version of a technology
called stream yard that is
sufficient to allow us to
interact,
Jannecke Øinæs: fascinating and
sort of from a higher
perspective, they will exist at
the same time.
Darryl Anka: Everything exists
now, because again, again, I
understand this as a heady
concept, and we use the analogy
of a hologram to sort of explain
it. It's not a full explanation,
but everything exists in the
same moment. There is only one
moment in existence, and that's
now. It's always now. No matter
what you do, it's always now.
And that is a real truth. It is
always here and it is always
now, no matter where you are, no
matter when you are, it's never
then. It's never will be. It's
always here and it's always now.
The idea is extended to the
concept of reducing space and
time to their simplest
components, which is sort of
what science does when they're
looking for a unified theory of
everything, they're looking for
one equation that explains
everything, which means it's a
reductive theory, which means
that they have to reduce how
something is explained to the
point where you can then explain
everything from the same single
equation, so to speak. Well,
metaphysics is no different. And
if you're going to reduce
things, you have to reduce space
and time as well. And the full
reduction of space is a single,
dimensionless point, and the
full reduction of time is a
single, timeless now. So that
translates as here and now.
Everything exists in that single
here and now. A moment I
understand our language can be
confusing when I use the word
moment, but what we perceive
therefore as different places
and different moments. It's the
same moment from another angle,
another point of view, because
there is only one moment to
perceive. There is only one
place to see, but looking at
that single place and that
single moment in time from a
different angle, a different
perspective, creates the
experience of different moments
in time, different places in
space, again, like a hologram. A
hologram is a photograph, a
three dimensional photograph,
but when you look at the
hologram itself, not the picture
on it, but the physical hologram
itself. It's just a flat piece
of celluloid. There's there's no
dimensionality to it at all. The
only reason it's that you see a
three dimensional object in the
hologram is because of the way
it was captured. Because when
you illuminate it from a
different angle, you see a
different side of the three
dimensional object. But all the
information of that object is
imprinted in that holographic
film everywhere. So it depends
on the angle you illuminate the
hologram from with your eyes.
That allows you to see what
appears to be a different angle
of the three dimensional object
that was initially photographed.
But all that information is in
the same place on the hologram.
It's all overlapping, and it
only depends on how you're
looking at it that determines
what side of that three
dimensional object you see. So
I'm saying reality is structured
like that.
Jannecke Øinæs: It is so
intelligent, my goodness. So
what can we look forward to if
we apply the five steps formula
as humans, and will that be us,
then opening up to this fourth
density that you refer to
Darryl Anka: absolutely because
when you act on your passion,
what does it do? It raises your
frequency. When you raise your
frequency, what happens? It
makes you a better receiver and
a better antenna for higher
frequency communication and
information. Remember, you can
only perceive what you are the
vibration of it's like Einstein
said, You cannot necessarily
solve a problem from the same
level of thinking in which the
problem was created. You have to
go to another level. So acting
on your passion raises your
frequency and makes you capable,
capable of even having thoughts
that exist on a higher level to
bring you the information you
need when you need it, that
helps you move forward in life
in a positive, constructive,
joyful, fulfilling way. So
acting on the five steps, acting
on the instruction manual of the
formula, allows you to
experience a life of more
synchronicity, more positive
experience, more freedom to be
who you really are, more
creativity, more love, more joy
and being really who you are as
a soul, allowing more of your
soul to express itself through
your physical form. That's what
it does. It makes your life more
effortless. It doesn't mean you
stop doing things. It just means
that when you do them, you're
doing acts of love, acts of joy.
You enjoy what you're doing. You
can't wait to get up in the
morning and start doing it again
and again and again. You start
being of service to others by
being a living example of what
they can do too. And they come
and ask, what are you doing?
What's your secret? How are you
living so happily? What are you
doing? How is it that it's
supporting you in life? Because,
again, it brings you everything
you need automatically, because
your soul is already putting out
that vibration that will attract
everything you need
automatically, if you just clean
out your attic of negative and
fear based beliefs and get out
of the way. So it's not
something you have to learn to
do. It's something you have to
allow to happen, but you have to
take the actions in physical
reality to demonstrate your
willingness and commitment to
allow it to happen, because this
is a physical experience. You
can't just wish it into being.
You have to act it into being,
because you are a physical
being, and action is the
language of physical reality.
You have to combine energy and
physical action to manifest so
manifest who you truly are by
taking the actions that are
representative of the actions
you would be taking if you
already lived in the world that
you prefer to live in, then
you're demonstrating to others
what that world looks like, and
they can then mirror you as
well, and you then suddenly
surround yourself with more
people doing the same thing,
thinking in similar ways, and
humanity. Then evolves in a
unified direction. It doesn't
mean everyone is the same. I'm
not talking about homogenizing
humanity. Unity is actually the
product of the validation of all
the true differences between us,
differences that are beneficial
and unique, that give us
different perspectives. So it's
not about flattening everything
out. It's about validating all
the differences and allowing
those differences to work
together in a beneficial way.
That's what the formula allows
you to experience.
Jannecke Øinæs: I have some
final questions.
Darryl Anka: Sure.
Jannecke Øinæs: Are we created
out of love? Is love what we are
Darryl Anka: my understanding in
bashar's interpretation, is that
what we call unconditional love
is the actual frequency of
existence itself. That's how we
interpret that frequency. So we
are immersed in that vibration
that we interpret as
unconditional love and support,
it doesn't have a mind of its
own. It supports us
unconditionally in whatever we
choose to believe is true for
us. We are allowed that freedom.
We are allowed that power to
choose, and whatever we choose,
negative or positive, we are
unconditionally supported and
loved in that choice. So yes,
we're immersed in the vibration
of existence, which we interpret
as unconditional love and
support
Jannecke Øinæs: beautiful what
is the most important question
we can ask ourselves at these
times?
Darryl Anka: Why? Why do I
believe what I believe? Let me
examine why I believe what I say
I believe is true. Because very
often, when you dig down into
the why, you find that you
sometimes don't really have a
good reason for believing what
you say you believe in you may
have picked it up from someone
else. It may have nothing to do
with you. I would always ask
why? To be certain that what you
say you prefer to believe in is
actually something that benefits
you, and you're not just
parroting a belief you picked up
along the way.
Jannecke Øinæs: What is the
deepest spiritual insight you
feel you have received from
Bashar?
Darryl Anka: Well, definitely
the formula, because that
changes everything. It's
literally a toolkit that you
apply and get a physical change
in your life. And to me, that's
the most profoundly powerful
gift that he could have given
us. Is something that actually
affects your physical reality
experience in a beneficial way.
No one has to believe that
Bashar is real. I can't prove
it. This could be coming from
another level of my own
consciousness. I don't know. But
of course, when open contact
occurs, we'll have all the proof
of extraterrestrials we need.
But that's not the reason why I
do this. It's because people
constantly come back to me and
say, hey, when I applied
bashar's formula in my life,
everything changed in the most
wonderful way. So the idea is,
if you apply the information,
you prove to yourself the
information actually works. It
actually has an effect. And I
can't think of anything more
important than having something
that actually gives you a
physical effect, that your life
has changed for the better. So
to me, that's the most profound
piece of information, you know,
aside from, I mean, there's
depth to it, because within the
formula, the deeper exploration
of it is understanding how
beliefs work, how we change
them, what they're all about,
how they perpetuate themselves,
all those kinds of things go
with it. What I've given you are
the five steps as a surface
representation. But when I say
one of the steps is examine your
beliefs and let them go, that
implies a very deep amount of
information about what beliefs
are, why they're created, how
they're changed, and all the
things that go with that. So
it's a deep understanding of how
our psychology works in physical
reality and how we can use it to
our benefit when we apply the
formula. But it goes much deeper
than the surface representation
I've just given you today.
Jannecke Øinæs: And my final
questions that I ask everyone,
and I asked the last time as
well, maybe I get a different
answer. What is self love to
you?
Darryl Anka: Daryl, self love is
knowing yourself as fully as
possible, as an aspect and a
reflection of source. And if you
exist and you are worthy in the
eyes of source just by the fact
that you exist because it needs
you to exist in order for it to
be all that it can be. Then if
it needs you. That much and
loves you that much, that you
need to be a part of it. Why
argue with it? Why not give that
to yourself? Why not recognize
that you are worthy and
deserving of loving yourself in
the same way that source is
supporting and unconditionally
loving you. Why would you argue
with it? You will never win that
argument. It can't stop
supporting you. It can't stop
loving you unconditionally. So
self love is simply the
recognition of sources love for
you, without arguing for the
opposite.
Jannecke Øinæs: I love that. And
what is the deepest meaning of
life from your perspective,
Darryl Anka: the meaning of
life, the deepest meaning of
life, ironically and
paradoxically, is that it has no
built in meaning. In other
words, everything is a set of
neutral props until you give it
meaning. You are designed to
give life meaning, and the
meaning you give it determines
the effect and experience you
get out of it. So the deepest
meaning of life is that life has
no built in meaning. It's your
job to give it meaning and give
it the experience that is
determined by the meaning you've
given it. That's the irony.
Jannecke Øinæs: Thank you so
much, Darrel, now if people
really want to dive deeper into
Bashar as teaching, could you
guide them? Where can they go?
Darryl Anka: They can go to
bashar.org, B, A, S, H, A,
R.org. Everything that Bashar
has talked about, or at least
most everything, is there that
can be accessed, and an
indication of all the events
coming up where he will deliver
more information is also listed
there. So bashar.org would be
the place to go to find out
anything about that. In the
upcoming year or so, we'll be
also teaching a class about
bashar's information, I myself
will be teaching that I've begun
to teach bits and pieces of that
class in different live events
that I've done around the
country, but I'll be putting
that all together, and that will
give people an opportunity in
joining that class to go deeper
into The different aspects of
the formula and all of Bashar is
teaching. Because, again, you
know, in any interview like
this, or any 90 minute event
that Bashar channels you can
only go so far, the class will
be hours and hours of really
digging deeply into that
information so that people can
really walk away understanding
and using and applying that
information in a very real way.
And again, when those classes
are available, it will be
announced at bashar.org so you
can check in there as well.
Jannecke Øinæs: Amazing. And I
also want to announce that you
can also meet Darrel and even
myself at the Sedona Ascension
Retreat in March 2026 and you
can also buy tickets online,
I've heard. Thank you so much,
Darryl, this is always such a
joy, and I learn so much each
time. It's so tangible, it's so
concrete, and I love that. Thank
you so much for spending time
with me and coming to the show,
and also for your amazing work,
Darryl Anka: absolutely and
thank you for yours, without
which this information wouldn't
be getting out there in the same
way. So I appreciate that, and
thank you for having me on. It's
always a pleasure.